<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ivothegreat on The Great Ivo Bolg</title><link>https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/tags/ivothegreat/</link><description>Recent content in Ivothegreat on The Great Ivo Bolg</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/tags/ivothegreat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We got comments!</title><link>https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/2025/comments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/2025/comments/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introducing-twikoo"&gt;Introducing Twikoo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What bolg would this be if it did not have any comment section? A shitty one, that&amp;rsquo;s what. So one of the first things I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on after officially publishing this bolg was figure out how to add comments. Guess I succeeded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="wow-ivo-thats-so-cool-how-did-you-do-it"&gt;Wow, Ivo, that&amp;rsquo;s so cool! How did you do it?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m glad you asked, fellow user. You see, this bolg is powered by Hugo (credited below). It&amp;rsquo;s a cool framework that just&amp;hellip; builds sites for you! Easy to install, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re on &lt;strong&gt;Linux&lt;/strong&gt;, and it needs few commands to get things done right. It also supports &lt;em&gt;themes&lt;/em&gt;. Those are custom layouts built by hardworking people so that lazy folks like me can just take them for their own websites. (This one site&amp;rsquo;s theme is also credited below.) Well, it seems that this theme integrates the front-end of two comment systems. From what I&amp;rsquo;ve understood, one of them is paid. As the genius Linus Torvalds once said:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hello, World!</title><link>https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/2025/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ivomiricribeiro.github.io/TheGreatIvoBolg/2025/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hello-world"&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess this is the first real post in this copy of a website. We&amp;rsquo;ll see if I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to actually commit to it. Knowing me, likely not. Nonetheless, stay tuned for future updates!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>